{
    "children": [
        {
            "children": [
                {
                    "children": [
                        {
                            "children": [
                                {
                                    "children": [],
                                    "question": "Since you are mutating the state, and you expect a render to take place, please check the location of the state update for any potential bugs in the implementation",
                                    "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                                    "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                                    "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                                    "infoDesc": "Render call expected"
                                },
                                {
                                    "children": [],
                                    "question": "Since you are mutating the state and you do not expect a render to take place, consider removing the state update call to resolve the bug",
                                    "thisAnswer": "No",
                                    "nodeType": "hypothesis",
                                    "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-state.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                                    "infoDesc": "Render call not expected"
                                }
                            ],
                            "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
                            "thisAnswer": "Yes",
                            "nodeType": "question",
                            "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                            "infoDesc": "Component mutates state"
                        },
                        {
                            "children": [],
                            "question": "Is a render expected to take place?",
                            "thisAnswer": "No",
                            "nodeType": "question",
                            "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/conditional-rendering.html#gatsby-focus-wrapper",
                            "infoDesc": "Component does not mutates state"
                        }
                    ],
                    "question": "Is this component mutating the state?",
                    "thisAnswer": "Function",
                    "nodeType": "question",
                    "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html",
                    "infoDesc": "Component is a Function"
                },
                {
                    "children": [],
                    "question": "Is this component mutating the state?",
                    "thisAnswer": "Class",
                    "nodeType": "question",
                    "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/state-and-lifecycle.html",
                    "infoDesc": "Component is a Class"
                }
            ],
            "question": "Is the bug in a function component or a class component?",
            "thisAnswer": "React",
            "nodeType": "question",
            "infoLink": "https://reactjs.org/docs/components-and-props.html#function-and-class-components",
            "infoDesc": "Framework used: React"
        },
        {
            "children": [],
            "question": "This is not supported yet",
            "thisAnswer": "Angular",
            "nodeType": "question",
            "infoLink": null,
            "infoDesc": "Framework used: Angular"
        },
        {
            "children": [],
            "question": "This is not supported yet",
            "thisAnswer": "Vue.js",
            "nodeType": "question",
            "infoLink": null,
            "infoDesc": "Framework used: Vue.js"
        },
        {
            "children": [],
            "question": "This is not supported yet",
            "thisAnswer": "Gatsby.js",
            "nodeType": "question",
            "infoLink": null,
            "infoDesc": "Framework used: Gatsby.js"
        }
    ],
    "question": "What framework or technology is being used here?",
    "thisAnswer": null,
    "nodeType": "question",
    "infoLink": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_framework",
    "infoDesc": null
}